

Elvis Wesley Vásquez Valarezo

Engineering in Electronics and Networks (Student) / Developer

Address: Los Olivos, Quito, Ecuador

Age: 25 yo

Telephone / cell: 0995988138 E-mail: elvis.vasquez@udla.edu.ec Github: https://github.com/wes9319

LinkedIn:https://www.linkedin.com/in/elvis-wesley-

vásquez-6b598474/

Personal Web: https://wes9319.github.io



For a complete and interactive experience, visit my website: https://wes9319.github.io Professional extract: My knowledge is oriented to technological areas mainly software, electronics and networks. I have held various positions as a developer (web, mobile), designer, community manager, project manager, network administrator, IT support, among others. My greatest strengths are proactivity, availability, commitment to my work, ability to work under pressure and management of common and technical English.



EXPERIENCE





Developer – Designer

Spae (Pre-university) 2014 - 2017

Functions: Development of the tailored institutional website, design of physical and digital advertising banners, community management (facebook, twitter, google +, instagram), design and administration of the internal network, IT support, teaching, assistance and development of multidisciplinary projects.

Community Manager - Multidisciplinary Project Developer

Spae - Freelance *2017*

Functions: Development of independent start-ups (Market to Home, Healthy Pet), brand design, community management (Facebook, Intagram), development of multidisciplinary projects (calculation, programming, statistics, electronics), web development on request, video editing and photography.

Web Developer – Proyect Leader

Magnaflor 2018-present

Functions: Full stack development (LAMP stack), Develop new custom functionalities(js, html, css, php) on the current platform, Development of new platform (Vue is), Web and Server management, Data analysis, Performance optimization.

See More...



EDUCATION •



▶ Udacity

Front-end web developer nanodegree 2015

Universidad de las Américas

Engineering in Electronics and Networks 2015 - present



SKILLS AND KNOWLEDGE



- ▶ Software development
- ▶ Networks(LAN, WAN)
- Analog Digital and **Electronics**
- Digital Marketing
- Multimedia Desian
- Database Administration
- Networking
- Leadership
- Integrity

LANGUAGES AND SOFTWARE 😊





Spanish (Native Language)

Advanced English)

Programming languages (C #, C, C ++, Java, swift, python, html, css, javascript, sql)

Operating systems (Windows, Linux, OSX)

Adobe Suite (Photoshop, Illustrator, Dreamweaver)

IDEs (Xcode, Visual Studio, Netbeans, Eclipse, SqlDeveloper, Arduino, Android Studio, etc.)

See more...